What did you want to do?
The footballer.
Very good.
And then I discovered that I was very stupid and
so I deviated and I met, I
met, I had the great fortune of
being able to meet Umberto Eco and then I
began to be interested in
semiotics and philosophy.  At a certain
point my dad Luigi got shingles
, the business was doing very
badly and so the only thing
I could do was help my dad
carry the suitcase and accompany him.
So we went to clients together and I
started taking wonderful trips
all over Italy and after a couple of trips
together I made my comments.  But did you
see?  we went to visit that
customer there, he replied like this, eh, but
why don't you make a product a little and he
started a dialogue and then to
help a father in difficulty, then I
approached the factory, but I didn't
ask for it, he didn't ask for it.
There was a silent rescue.